Guide to the Eldon Barrett Papers 1849-2010
Western Washington University, Heritage Resources
- Materials: Research and Writings, 1849-2012; 1937-2009; Series II.
  - Publications
    - Appaloosa, 1964-1981 (Box-folder 9/6)
    - All in days work (Reader’s Digest), 1984 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - Seattle/Puget Sound Business Journals, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Blowing in the wind (kites), 1982-1989 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Perspective on planes, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - Book reviews, 1964-1997 (Box-folder 9/11)
    - A ride with the ‘Wild Breadman’, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 9/12)
    - Brock Adams, 1977 (Box-folder 9/13)
    - Buggy Business (Ladybugs), 1967-1970 (Box-folder 9/14)
    - Business week, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 9/15)
    - Carefree Copenhagen and Sweden, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 9/16)
    - Chippie and the Chinook, 1970-1985 (Box-folder 9/17)
    - "Of Bears, Squeeks, and Timberbeasts and How to Choke a Herring"(Volume Three) by Eldon Barrett, 2012 July (Box-folder 9/18)
  - Published articles
    - Christmas conjunction, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 9/19)
    - Christmas trees (“Shelton: Sultan of Swag”), 1965-1980 (Box-folder 9/20)
    - Clam funny (filler), 1967 (Box-folder 9/21)
    - Diamond Lil, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 9/22)
    - Dishwasher salmon, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 9/23)
    - Jean Enerson “At home on KING-TV”, 1988 (Box-folder 9/24)
    - Fillers (used), 1967-1996 (Box-folder 9/25)
    - Gingerbread, 1989 (Box-folder 9/26)
    - Tilting-top table “George Washington ate here”, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 9/27)
    - Herald specials, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 9/28)
    - Island hopping on Puget Sound, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 9/29)
    - Latin lover, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 9/30)
    - Legislature (humor), 1965-1983 (Box-folder 9/31)
    - Professor Loftus (fires), 1982 (Box-folder 9/32)
    - Hay Lewis (people’s choice), 1966-2002 (Box-folder 9/33)
    - Logger lingo, 1963-1984 (Box-folder 9/34)
    - Logging boots, 1990 (Box-folder 9/35)
    - Low-interest tax loans, 1980 (Box-folder 9/36)
    - Lutefisk, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 9/37)
    - Lynden, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 9/38)
    - The Maine is remembered (hiker’s park), 1978-1988 (Box-folder 9/39)
    - Matanuska, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 9/40)
    - Mima mounds, 1974 (Box-folder 9/41)
    - Monster roster, 2001 (Box-folder 9/42)
    - Never say die, 1964-1981 (Box-folder 9/43)
    - Nostalgia columns, 1989 (Box-folder 9/44)
    - Olympic Peninsula, 1982-2005 (Box-folder 9/45)
    - "Personal Privilege""Deal," (Box-folder 9/46)
    - Pulse publications, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 9/47)
    - Reader’s Digest filler, 1986 (Box-folder 9/48)
    - Seavest, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 9/49)
    - Septober in Alaska, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 9/50)
    - Ski to Sea, 1987 (Box-folder 9/51)
    - Slainte, 1986 (Box-folder 9/52)
    - State Seal, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 9/53)
    - Steelhead, 1967-1989 (Box-folder 9/54)
    - Tansy Ragwort, 1985 (Box-folder 9/55)
    - Vanport flood, 1948; 1978 (Box-folder 9/56)
    - Western Avenue, 1977 (Box-folder 9/57)
    - Memories… and other stories Volume 1 by Eldon Barrett, 2009 (Box-folder 9/58)
- Slides, Photographs and Scrapbooks, 1930-1999; 1960-1999; Series III.
  - Slides – Bellingham/Whatcom County (1of 2), circa 1986-1998 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Slides – Bellingham/Whatcom County (2of 2), circa 1986-1998 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Slides – Oregon (1of 2), circa 1985-1996 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Slides – Oregon (2of 2), circa 1985-1996 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Slides – Flora, Fauna, Sun Shots, Autumn (1 of 2), circa 1972-1996 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Slides – Flora, Fauna, Sun Shots, Autumn (1 of 2), circa 1972-1996 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Slides – Mt. St. Helens, Mt. Rainier, North Cascades etc. (1 of 2), circa 1984-1999 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Slides – Mt. St. Helens, Mt. Rainier, North Cascades etc. (1 of 2), circa 1984-1999 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - UPI – Editor’s Notebook, circa 1969-1984 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - UPI – Editor’s Notebook, circa 1966-1970 (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Photo Album contains pictures of Seattle, Robert F. Kennedy, Presidents, Black Panthers in Olympia, circa 1960s-1990 (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Photo Album: pictures of Washington State, Alaska, Greece, Italy, undated (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Black and White 35mm Negatives include photos of famous people and various places around the United States, undated (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Black and White 35mm Negatives: Portland, Seattle, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, Victoria, British Columbia, Canada, Bellingham, undated (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Slides – Various places and events from around the World (1 of 2), circa 1960s-1970s (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Slides – Various places and events from around the World (2 of 2), circa 1960s-1970s (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Seattle World’s Fair Official Press Book, 1962 (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Photos and Clippings File (1 of 2): Eldon Barrett – On The Job, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 11/8)
  - Photos and Clippings File (2 of 2): Eldon Barrett – On The Job, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 11/9)
  - UPI Notebook – High School reports and World War II papers, circa 1930s-1950s (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Photographs, Press Corp (Salem and Seattle), 1946-1948 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Photographs, S.S. North Coast and Crew, U.S.S. Mississippi (Box-folder 11/12)
  - Photograph, Other (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Slides – Alaska & Alaska Indians (1 of 2), circa 1971-1996 (Box-folder 11/14)
  - Slides – Alaska & Alaska Indians (2 of 2), circa 1971-1996 (Box-folder 11/15)
  - Slides Box 1 (contains images of Seattle, Green Lake, RFK, politicians, Bellingham Bay, Boats) (Box-folder 11b/16)
  - Slides Box 2 (contains images of Ferries, Gold Cup Race, Seattle, WWU Alumni Race, Pike Place Market), 1970 (Box-folder 11b/17)
  - Slides – Olympic Penninsula – Port Townsend – Washington Coast – Olympia (1 of 2), circa 1971-1996 (Box-folder 11b/18)
  - Slides – Olympic Penninsula – Port Townsend – Washington Coast – Olympia (2 of 2), circa 1971-1996 (Box-folder 11b/19)
  - Envelope of 4 x 6 in. negatives “Ellis C. Ayer” (CD of digitized images included in folder), undated (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Photos and Slides (Various world-wide locations and Seattle), circa 1960s-1970s (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Photos and Slides (Various world-wide locations and Seattle), circa 1960s-1970s (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Amchitka and more, circa 1971-1974 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Newspaper scrapbook of Eldon Barrett clippings, press credentials, business cards, etc., circa 1970s to 1980 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Black and White photographs including images of Native Americans and locations around the world, undated (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Slides – Eastern Washington, Idaho, Montana, (1 of 2), circa 1974-1996 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Slides – Eastern Washington, Idaho, Montana, (2 of 2), circa 1974-1996 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Loose color prints (5 sheets) Bellingham/Whatcom County, undated (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Slides – Top Pix Miscellaneous, circa 1962-1998 (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Slides – Canada (1 of 2), circa 1966-1998 (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Slides – Canada (2 of 2), circa 1966-1998 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - Color photographs and negatives includes – WWU Sculptures, WWU, Whatcom County, VRI, undated (Box-folder 13/1)
  - Loose postcards, undated (Box-folder 13/2)
- Event Programs, 1961-1980; Series IV.
  - Dedication Ceremony and Pageant Program “The Spirit of America” The Kingdome, March 27, 1976 (Box-folder 13/3)
  - NBA All Star Game Program, January 15, 1974 (Box-folder 13/4)
  - Pat Boone Celebrity Golf Classic Ocean Shores, Washington Program, 1968 (Box-folder 13/5)
  - University of Washington Academic Centennial Convocation Proceedings Program, November 16, 1961 (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1875-1990 (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Boeing Magazine, September 1970 (Box-folder 13/8)
  - United States National Viewpoint Statement on the Environment, August 15, 1974 (Box-folder 13/9)
  - USA 76: The First Two Hundred Years Bicentennial Program, 1976 (Box-folder 13/10)
  - Icemen: A History of the Western Hockey League, circa 1972 (Box-folder 13/11)
  - The Dong Show: Puget Sound Sportswriters and Sportscasters Association 28th Annual Mid-Winter Sports Banquet Program, February 6, 1978 (Box-folder 13/12)
  - Seattle Mariners Official 1978 Scorecard (Box-folder 13/13)
  - The Kingdome Magazine, March 1976 (Box-folder 13/14)
  - Alaska Pictorial Panorama, 1967 (Box-folder 13/15)
  - The Worlds of Alaska, 1980 (Box-folder 13/16)
  - Introduction to Alaska 1972 with photo review… “Cities of the North” (Box-folder 13/17)
  - The Alaska Journal Vol. 3 Nos. 1-4, 1973 (Box-folder 13/18)
  - Alaska Today Volumes 1 and 2, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 13/19)
  - Seattle Pilots Official Scorebook, April 1969 (Box-folder 13/20)
  - "Indians in Washington" Published by Victor A. Meyers Secretary of State, Undated (Box-folder 13/21)
  - "Southern Alberta's Roamin' Empire" By Ken Liddell Frontier Book No. 6, Undated (Box-folder 13/22)
  - "Strangers on the Land" Yakima Treaty of 1855, 1962 (Box-folder 13/23)
  - Olympia Washington Centennial Program, 1950 (Box-folder 13/24)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Headlines
  - "Headlines of History from the Seattle Post-Intelligencer"(11.5"x15.5"), 1975 (Oversized-box 1)
  - Newspaper Scrapbook (16"x12"x2")
  - Framed Certificate "Project Cannikin", Undated (Oversized-box 2)
  - Certificate from the Rice Systems of Business Penmanship
  - "Welcome to Nautilus", June 15, 1957